A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1957
  - Europe, 1957; 1957/700
    - Europe - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/700.S
      - Europe - "Diary of a trip to Europe" - Erskine W. McKinley, Oct 22-Dec 14, 1957 (Box 69, Folder 0454B)
  - Austria, 1957; 1957/705
    - Austria - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 454)
    - Austria - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 455)
  - Belgium, 1957; 1957/707
    - Belgium - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 456)
    - Belgium - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/707.A
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 456)
    - Belgium - Nursing, 1957; 1957/707.C
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 456)
    - Belgium - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/707.E
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 456)
    - Belgium - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/707.S
      - Belgium - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 456)
  - Yugoslavia, 1957; 1957/710
    - Yugoslavia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
    - Yugoslavia - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/710.A
      - Yugoslavia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
    - Yugoslavia - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/710.D
      - Yugoslavia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
    - Yugoslavia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/710.E
      - Yugoslavia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
  - Bulgaria, 1957; 1957/711
    - Bulgaria - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
  - Czechoslovakia, 1957; 1957/712
    - Czechoslovakia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 457)
  - Denmark, 1957; 1957/713
    - Denmark - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 458)
    - Denmark - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/713.E
      - Denmark - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 458)
  - Iceland, 1957; 1957/715
    - Iceland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 458)
  - Germany, 1957; 1957/717
    - Germany - (A - P), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 459)
    - Germany - (R - Z), 1957 (Box 69, Folder 460)
    - Germany - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/717.D
      - Germany - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 461)
    - Germany - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/717.E
      - Germany - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 461)
    - Germany - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/717.S
      - Germany - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 461)
  - Greece, 1957; 1957/749
    - Greece - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 462)
    - Greece - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/749.A
      - Greece - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 462)
    - Greece - Nursing, 1957; 1957/749.C
      - Greece - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 462)
    - Greece - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/749.E
      - Greece - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 462)
    - Greece - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/749.S
      - Greece - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 462)
  - Hungary, 1957; 1957/750
    - Hungary, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 463)
    - Hungary - (A-K), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 464)
    - Hungary - (L-Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 465)
    - Hungary - Nursing, 1957; 1957/750.C
      - Hungary - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 466)
    - Hungary - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/750.E
      - Hungary, 1957 (Box 70, Folder 463)
      - Hungary - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 466)
  - Italy, 1957; 1957/751
    - Italy - (A - T), 1957 (Box 70, Folder 467)
    - Italy - International University for Social Studies, Rome, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 468)
    - Italy - UNLA, 1957 (Box 71, Folder 469)
    - Italy - (U - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 470)
    - Italy - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/751.A
      - Italy - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 471)
    - Italy - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/751.D
      - Italy - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 471)
    - Italy - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/751.E
      - Italy - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 471)
    - Italy - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/751.S
      - Italy - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 471)
  - Norway, 1957; 1957/767
    - Norway - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 472)
    - Norway - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/767.E
      - Norway - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 472)
    - Norway - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/767.R
      - Norway - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 472)
    - Norway - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/767.S
      - Norway - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 472)
  - Iran, 1957; 1957/771
    - Iran - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 71, Folder 473)
  - Portugal, 1957; 1957/773
    - Portugal - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
    - Portugal - Nursing, 1957; 1957/773.C
      - Portugal - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
    - Portugal - Malaria, 1957; 1957/773.I
      - Portugal - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
  - Rumania, 1957; 1957/783
    - Roumania - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
  - Russia, 1957; 1957/785
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
  - Finland, 1957; 1957/787
    - Finland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
    - Finland - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/787.A
      - Finland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
    - Finland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/787.E
      - Finland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 474)
  - Poland, 1957; 1957/789
    - Poland - (A - O), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 475)
    - Poland - (P - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 476)
    - Poland - Nursing, 1957; 1957/789.C
      - Poland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 476)
    - Poland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/789.E
      - Poland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 477)
    - Poland - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/789.R
      - Poland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 477)
  - Spain, 1957; 1957/795
    - Spain - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 478)
    - Spain - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/795.A
      - Spain - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 478)
    - Spain - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/795.E
      - Spain - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 478)
    - Spain - Malaria, 1957; 1957/795.I
      - Spain - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 478)
  - Sweden, 1957; 1957/800
    - Sweden - (A - R), 1957 (Box 72, Folder 479)
    - Sweden - (S - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 480)
    - Sweden - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/800.A
      - Sweden - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 480)
    - Sweden - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/800.D
      - Sweden - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 480)
    - Sweden - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/800.E
      - Sweden - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 480)
    - Sweden - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/800.R
      - Sweden - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 480)
  - Switzerland, 1957; 1957/803
    - Switzerland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 481)
    - Switzerland - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/803.E
      - Switzerland - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 481)
  - Near East Region, 1957; 1957/804
    - Near East Region - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 482)
    - Near East Region - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/804.R
      - Near East Region - "Diary of a trip to the Near East" - John Marshall, Mar 1-31, 1957 (Box 73, Folder 483)
  - Turkey, 1957; 1957/805
    - Turkey - (A - I), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 484)
    - Turkey - (K - P), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 485)
    - Turkey - (R - Z), 1957 (Box 73, Folder 486)
    - Turkey - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/805.A
      - Turkey - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 487)
    - Turkey - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/805.D
      - Turkey - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 487)
    - Turkey - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/805.E
      - Turkey - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 487)
    - Turkey - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/805.R
      - Turkey - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 487)
    - Turkey - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/805.S
      - Turkey - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 487)
  - Jordan, 1957; 1957/816
    - Jordan - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/816.A
      - Jordan - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
    - Jordan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/816.E
      - Jordan - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
  - Saudi Arabia and Oman, 1957; 1957/817
    - Saudi Arabia and Oman - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
  - Palestine / Israel, 1957; 1957/825
    - Israel - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
    - Palestine / Israel - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/825.A
      - Israel - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
    - Palestine / Israel - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/825.D
      - Israel - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 488)
  - Lebanon, 1957; 1957/833
    - Lebanon - (A - K), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 489)
    - Lebanon - (L - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 490)
    - Lebanon - Nursing, 1957; 1957/833.C
      - Lebanon - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 490)
    - Lebanon - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/833.E
      - Lebanon - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 490)
    - Lebanon - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/833.S
      - Lebanon - (A - Z), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 490)
  - Administration, 1957; 1957/900
    - Administration, 1957 (Box 74, Folder 491)
  - Trustees, 1957; 1957/903
    - Members and Meetings - (Bingham - Kimberly), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 492)
    - Members and Meetings - Loeb, Robert F., 1957 (Box 74, Folder 493)
    - Members and Meetings - (Lovett - McKelway), 1957 (Box 74, Folder 494)
    - Members and Meetings - Moe, Henry Allen, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 495)
    - Members and Meetings - (Myers - Wood), 1957 (Box 75, Folder 496)
    - Members and Meetings - Consultants, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 497)
    - Members and Meetings - Consultants - Candidates, 1957 (Box 75, Folder 498)